{
  "extraDescription": "for nonnegative fractions, in which the denominators are the same or one of the denominators is 1",
  "openingRemarks": "NB: you can give answers as unsimplified fractions.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(3 - \\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "5/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{11} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "3/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{5} - \\dfrac{2}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{11} - \\dfrac{2}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "5/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + \\dfrac{5}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "9/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-3/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + \\dfrac{9}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "17/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{5} + \\dfrac{12}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "21/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{11}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-2/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} + \\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + \\dfrac{7}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "12/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{5} + \\dfrac{4}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "11/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} - 1\\)",
      "answer": "-1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{2} - 3\\)",
      "answer": "-3/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{2}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "8/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{5} + 1\\)",
      "answer": "7/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4} - \\dfrac{11}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-5/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{12} + \\dfrac{11}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{7} - \\dfrac{5}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} + 2\\)",
      "answer": "9/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + \\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "21/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} + \\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{11} + \\dfrac{7}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "13/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{11} + \\dfrac{7}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "14/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} + 1\\)",
      "answer": "3/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{3} - 2\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10 - \\dfrac{1}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "119/12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{7} + \\dfrac{2}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "4/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{9} + \\dfrac{2}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "10/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{4} - \\dfrac{7}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{11} + \\dfrac{7}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "12/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} + 4\\)",
      "answer": "13/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{3} + \\dfrac{8}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + \\dfrac{1}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "9/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + \\dfrac{5}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "53/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{8} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "11/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{11} + \\dfrac{3}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "6/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - \\dfrac{11}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-11/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{8} - \\dfrac{9}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{9} + \\dfrac{8}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "19/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{7} + \\dfrac{12}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - \\dfrac{11}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-11/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{3} - \\dfrac{7}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "4/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{3} - \\dfrac{8}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-4/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{3} - \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - \\dfrac{7}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "-7/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{4} - 2\\)",
      "answer": "3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + \\dfrac{1}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "22/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} + 4\\)",
      "answer": "13/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{3} - \\dfrac{11}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-4/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{5} + \\dfrac{2}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + \\dfrac{9}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "9/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{3} - \\dfrac{11}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{11} + \\dfrac{8}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "18/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{5} - \\dfrac{12}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-6/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{11} - \\dfrac{8}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-5/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{8} + \\dfrac{3}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{3} - \\dfrac{5}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + \\dfrac{7}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "13/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{9} + \\dfrac{5}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "16/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{2} + 2\\)",
      "answer": "13/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{2} + \\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{11} + \\dfrac{6}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "8/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{11} + \\dfrac{5}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "14/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - \\dfrac{1}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4} - \\dfrac{7}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{11} + \\dfrac{3}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "9/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + \\dfrac{5}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "5/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 - \\dfrac{7}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{11} + \\dfrac{6}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{1}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{7} - \\dfrac{11}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-8/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{11} + \\dfrac{8}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "10/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{7} + \\dfrac{12}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "16/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4} + \\dfrac{5}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "3/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{12} + \\dfrac{7}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{6} - \\dfrac{7}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "-1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4} - 1\\)",
      "answer": "-1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{7} - \\dfrac{9}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "2/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{11} - 1\\)",
      "answer": "-2/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + \\dfrac{10}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "19/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} + 3\\)",
      "answer": "7/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{5} - \\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{2} + \\dfrac{7}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + \\dfrac{5}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "11/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 - \\dfrac{1}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "5/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{7}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + \\dfrac{7}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "18/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + \\dfrac{2}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "12/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + \\dfrac{11}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "21/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - \\dfrac{8}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-8/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{7}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-5/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{9} - \\dfrac{10}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{6} - \\dfrac{5}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 - \\dfrac{9}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "3/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    }
  ]
}
